laptoppartsexpert.com 2007-12-24

# Laptop Parts Expert Privacy Policy

|  |   |   
---|---  
|   
| 

**PRIVACY POLICIES**

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
  
---  
  
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.laptoppartsexpert.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.  
2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your personal information.  
3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.  
4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g.: to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

1\. See what information we have about you, if any,  
2\. Change/correct any data we have about you,  
3\. Have us delete and data we have about you,  
4\. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g.: billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you request something from a Laptop Parts Expert website, for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information, with others, for instance, other parts of Laptop Parts Expert, Laptop Parts Expert Business Partners, financial institutions, shipping companies, postal or government authorities (e.g.: Customs authorities) involved in fulfillment. In connection with a transaction we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes ONLY.

Our top priority is making sure you can shop safely in our store.

When you place an order in our store, Laptop Parts Expert protects your credit card number and personal information by encrypting it. Encryption scrambles your information. This information stays scrambled while traveling over the Internet between our server's and your computer. All transactions use the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) / 128 bit encryption protocol when transmitting information over secure ports.

Laptop Parts Expert is also 

[registered with Verisign](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&type=GOLD&sealid=2&dn=WWW.LAPTOPPARTS.COM&lang=en), the industry leader in website identification. This means that your browser can confirm Laptop Parts Expert’s identity before transmitting your personal information.

**Orders**  
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and order fulfillment. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.   
  
**SAFE SHOPPING**  
  
Safe, secure shopping 24 hours a day! Our top priority is making sure you can shop safely in our store. Our Secure Shopper Guarantee means you don't have to worry about the safety of your credit card information.

When you place an order in our store, Laptop Parts Expert protects your credit card number and personal information by encrypting it. Encryption scrambles your information. This information stays scrambled while traveling over the Internet and remains scrambled even while stored on Laptop Parts Expert’s servers. All transactions use the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) / 128 bit encryption protocol when transmitting information over secure ports.

Laptop Parts Expert is also registered with Verisign, the industry leader in website identification. This means that your browser can confirm Laptop Parts Expert’s identity before transmitting any personal information.
